class DummyDb {
  static List<Map<String, dynamic>> questions = [
   
    {
      "question": "Which method is used to update the UI in StatefulWidget?",
      "options": ["build()", "initState()", "setState()", "dispose()"],
      "answerIndex": 2, // setState()
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Flutter widget is used to render a piece of text?",
      "options": ["Container", "Row", "Text", "Scaffold"],
      "answerIndex": 2, // Text
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of the 'pubspec.yaml' file in Flutter?",
      "options": [
        "Define the project’s assets and dependencies",
        "Store app UI components",
        "Contain compiled code",
        "Manage device storage"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0, // Define the project’s assets and dependencies
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which widget is commonly used for creating app layouts in Flutter?",
      "options": ["Scaffold", "Stack", "AppBar", "Drawer"],
      "answerIndex": 0, // Scaffold
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Flutter primarily used for?",
      "options": [
        "Web development",
        "Mobile app development",
        "Desktop app development",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 3, // All of the above
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company developed Flutter?",
      "options": ["Apple", "Microsoft", "Google", "Facebook"],
      "answerIndex": 2, // Google
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What is the main language used to write Flutter applications?",
      "options": ["JavaScript", "Python", "Swift", "Dart"],
      "answerIndex": 3, // Dart
    },
    {
      "question":
          "In Flutter, which widget is used to add padding around a child widget?",
      "options": ["Padding", "Center", "Align", "Column"],
      "answerIndex": 0, // Padding
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Flutter package is widely used for state management?",
      "options": ["dio", "provider", "url_launcher", "http"],
      "answerIndex": 1, // provider
    },
    {
      "question": "What widget is used to create scrollable lists in Flutter?",
      "options": ["Column", "Row", "ListView", "Container"],
      "answerIndex": 2, // ListView
    },
  ];
}
